The CIA is constantly pushing the the
envelope of legality and they just wait
for somebody to push back. The reason
why the Russians haven't agreed to
substantive talks brokered by Donald
Trump is that they're winning so that it
is now legal for the American government
to propagandize the American people.
Every one of them has seen something.
Some ship sometimes they're coming out
of the water. you know that I probably
shouldn't comment on.
>> So what do you feel about the situation
that's occurring in Israel and Gaza and
even after the ceasefire um the deaths
that have been occurring and and the
civilians and military casualty
proportions? How do you feel about this
situation? And why do you think that the
West and particularly the US is so
complacent in their response?
>> Um I I I feel that this is a genocide. I
think it's very clear that it's a
genocide. It meets every definition of a
genocide, including ethnic cleansing.
Um,
I don't believe there has been a a
ceasefire because the Israelis have
continued to kill Palestinian civilians
quite literally every single day since
the so-called ceasefire uh was
initiated.
And um
and I think the reason why the United
States,
you know, I hesitate to use the word
complacent because complacency implies
disinterest.
>> I'm going to say
I think the reason why the US is
a part of this and it's on the side of
of the Israelis and Israeli actions in
both Gaza and the West Bank is that the
pro-Israel lobby in the United States is
so strong that almost no one has the
guts to stand up to Israel. You know,
there are Israeli lobbyists in literally
every single one of the 535
U members of Congress on Capitol Hill.
There are Israeli lobbyists in literally
every single one of the 50 state
legislatures. And now we have Israeli
lobbyists lobbying at the um at the
local level.
Why why do Israelis care
about the outcome of American
schoolboard races? Or who gets elected
mayor of what town?
or who gets elected to some little teeny
tiny district in Kansas or Arizona.
It doesn't make sense to me unless it's
a concerted effort to control American
foreign policy, which I I believe that
it is.
>> Do you think that um the attacks on
Iran, for example, are proof of um the
fact that Israeli influences, Apac,
other lobbyist groups might want to
control American policy. Oh yeah. Yeah.
Iran is not a threat to the United
States. Period. I state that as fact.
States. The Iranians don't have weapons
to attack the United States. And even if
they had weapons, they don't have
delivery systems to attack the United
States. They're a threat to Israel. Why?
Because Israel is a threat to them.
Somebody said something to me the other
day and it was so simple and it made
such sense. Why are we not talking about
North Korea right now? I can tell you
why. Because North Korea has a nuclear
weapon.
So, nobody's going to attack North
Korea. Because they don't want North
Korea to attack them. That's why the
Iranians have sought a nuclear weapon.
Well, I mean, the CIA says that they
actually haven't sought a nuclear
weapon. But were they to seek one,
it's to protect themselves against the
Israelis. the Israelis who have dozens
apparently dozens of nuclear weapons.
>> And in terms of the intelligence
cooperation between the US and Israel,
how how deep does this go?
>> You know, that I probably shouldn't
comment on.
>> Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
Um,
so I if this is something you can't
comment on as well, then I can um cut it
from the interview or whatever, but in
in the case of October the 7th,
>> do you see it as an intelligence
breakdown or comp political complacency
or something else? I mean, I know we
have the Hannibal directive, but what
what would you say about this?
>> I I'm of two minds about October 7th. On
the one hand, it was clear for two or
three weeks in advance of the attack
that something was a foot. There were
settlers who were warning Jerusalem that
an attack was coming. But these two
morons, ministers Bengavir and uh and uh
Smootrich
who are in charge of security
apparently believed say they believed
that the attack was going to come in the
West Bank, not in Gaza and that's why
they were unprepared. That's one side of
the story. The other side, and I think
there's probably something to this, was
this attack on October 7th gave the
Israeli government the green light to
utterly destroy Gaza.
Destroy it. There are probably 200,000
people dead. Officially, there are
69,000. We have no idea how many dead
remain under the rubble just as
skeletons now. But I think that was the
whole plan was to completely destroy
Gaza and to throw out literally all of
the Palestinians so that the whole area
could be resettled
with with uh Israelis.
>> And do you think there's any way of um
Hamas and the Israeli government coming
to a a proper effective ceasefire or a
peace plan or a two-state solution? Or
do you think that the Israelis just
aren't interested in that?
>> No. Benjamin Netanyahu very proudly said
the other day that he killed the
two-state solution. There is no
two-state solution.
It's gone. And it's gone because he
killed it. So, no, Hamas is, you know, a
handful of guys with long beards. U the
Israelis are murdering civilians, women,
children, the elderly, the sick. And you
can't have as a viable policy to just
kill everybody. The Israelis of all
people in the world should know
something like that. Um, and so I I
don't think there's any chance of a of a
true ceasefire. I don't think there's
any chance of of a real peace. Look,
when the Israelis continue to bomb
uh the Palestinian negotiating team
while they're in other countries,
there won't be any peace. No.
>> Mhm. And do you think in terms of the
political influence that um Israel has
in the US, do you think that there's any
way to mitigate this or try and reverse
this or do you think it's just too
embedded into every area of US politics?
It's a combination of being embedded and
and also of senior policy makers not
having any problem with it. Donald Trump
has no problem with the Israelis running
US foreign policy and Joe Biden also
didn't have a problem with that.
>> No. And and Barack Obama and George W.
Bush and they all just accept that that
Benjamin Netanyahu is going to run
American foreign policy.
I mean, I I think this will lead on to
some of my um
next questions, but do you think that
there's a reason for this beyond the
common claim that Israel is our greatest
ally and Israel is a point of strength
in the Middle East?
>> Sure. It's money. It's money. If if you
are not 1,000% pro-Israeli,
if you are not an ardent Zionist, they
will spend millions of dollars to defeat
you in an election. And more often than
not, they're successful.
So if you have any hopes for a political
career in the United States, you have to
be ardently and publicly Zionist.